Division of Invertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Divisional Correspondence, 1866-2011; Series VI
  - Robinson Verrill Correspondence. Correspondence from Robinson Verrill., 1962; 001164
    - Robinson Verrill Correspondence. A letter from R. Verrill to S.D. Ripley, Museum Director thanking him for the invitation to the award ceremonies of the Addison E. Verrill medal. He enloses 6 letters written by his grandfather Byron D. Verrill to Byron's brother, Addison E. Verrill. The 6 letters have been cataloged as A.E. Verrill Correspondence., 02 Nov 1962; 001165
- Miscellaneous Specimen Lists, 1864-Present; Series VII
  Miscellaneous lists of specimens.
  - Miscellaneous., 1864-Present; 006521
    - Miscellaneous list of branchiopods. List from Tom Hegna regarding specimens of large branchiopod used for SEM, 29 may 2008; 006522
  - Musuem of Comparative Zoology Coral Type Specimens. List of MCZ coral type specimens., 1864-Present; 002016
    - Musuem of Comparative Zoology Coral Type Specimens. A digital list of MCZ coral type specimens., 1980 - 1989; 002017
  - Non-Invertebrate Lists. Miscellaneous lists of Non-Invertebrates., 1864-Present; 001346
    - Non-Invertebrate Lists. List of fishes from the Smithsonian., 08 Mar 1872; 001538
    - Non-Invertebrate Lists. A list of Birds sent to C.A. Houghton to be mounted. Specimens marked were returned 25 Jun 1878., 12 Dec 1877 - 25 Jun 1878; 001348
    - Non-Invertebrate Lists. Australian brid skins from Capt. Porter. See VZA.000328., 1872; 001350
    - Non-Invertebrate Lists. Lists of North American Birds for Cases 1-4. Possibly for public exhibit?, 001347
    - Non-Invertebrate Lists. A list of bird species. Note on the top of the list says "Catalogued", 001349
- Staff and Affiliates, 1864-Present; Series VIII
  Archives related to divisional staff and affiliates.
  - Charlotte Bush Payslips. Payslips of Charlotte Bush., 1885 - 1888; 001485
    - Charlotte Bush Payslips. Payslips of Charlotte Bush for services rendered Aug 1885 through Mar 1888. In C.E. Bush hand., Aug 1885 - Mar 1888; 001487
  - Dr. Gordon A. Riley. Gordon A. Riley Papers., 1911-1985; 001957
    - Dr. Gordon A. Riley. An unpublished manuscript, titled "Reminiscences of an Oceanographer." 136 pages., 1984; 001958
  - Dr. Kensuke Yanagi. Note from Dr. Yanagi during his visit in March 2014., 002798
    - Dr. Kensuke Yanagi. Notes written by Dr. Kensuke Yanagi during his stay at Yale Peabody Museum, Division of Invertebrate Zoology. Notes on Actiniaria types, A. E. Verril and W. Stimpson, March 2014; 002797
  - Katherine Bush Payslips. Payslips of Katherine Bush., 1885 - 1888; 001486
    - Katherine Bush Payslips. Payslips of Katherine Bush for services rendered from Jan 1885 to Jan 1888. In K.J. Bush hand., Jan 1885 - Jan 1888; 001488
  - Photographs., 1864-Present; 001473
    - Photographs. Two pictures of Rudy Freund., 1960-1969; 001474
    - Photographs. Picture of Susan and Bob Borden. Digital only., 2009; 005656
    - Photographs. Flora B. Verrill, 005657
  - Rudolf Freund Suriname Photographs. Rudy Freund Suriname Photographs., 005939
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 2: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005940
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 3: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005941
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 4: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005942
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 5: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005943
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 6: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005944
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 7: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005945
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 9: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005946
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 10: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005947
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 12: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005948
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 13: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005949
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 14: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005950
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 15: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005951
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 17: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005952
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 19: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005953
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 20: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005954
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 22: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005955
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 24: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005956
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 25: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005957
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 26: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005958
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 28: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005959
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 30: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005960
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 31: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005961
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 33: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005962
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 35: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005963
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 36: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005964
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 1 Slide 38: Trinidad going Saramacca River Paramaribo., 005965
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 2: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005966
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 3: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005967
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 4: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005968
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 6: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005969
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 7: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005970
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 8: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005971
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 9: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005972
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 10: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005973
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 12: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005974
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 14: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005975
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 15: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005976
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 16: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005977
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 17: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005978
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 19: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005979
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 21: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005980
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 22: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005981
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 23: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005982
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 24: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005983
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 25: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005984
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 27: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005985
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 28: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005986
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 30: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005987
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 33: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005988
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 34: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005989
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 36: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005990
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 37: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005991
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 2 Slide 38: Market & Streets of Paramaribo., 005992
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 1: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005993
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 2: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005994
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 3: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005995
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 4: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005996
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 5: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005997
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 7: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005998
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 8: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 005999
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 10: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006000
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 11: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006001
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 12: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006002
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 13: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006003
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 14: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006004
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 16: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006005
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 18: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006006
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 19: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006007
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 21: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006008
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 22: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006009
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 24: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006010
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 25: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006011
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 27: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006012
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 28: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006013
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 30: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006014
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 31: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006015
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 32: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006016
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 33: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006017
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 34: Market & Paramaribo Streets., 006018
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 3 Slide 37: Market & Paramaribo Streets, 006019
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 2: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006020
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 4: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006021
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 5: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006022
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 6: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006023
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 7: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006024
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 9: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006025
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 10: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006026
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 11: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006027
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 12: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006028
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 13: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006029
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 14: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006030
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 15: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006031
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 16: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006032
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 17: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006033
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 19: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006034
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 20: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006035
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 21: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006036
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 23: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006037
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 25: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006038
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 27: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006039
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 29: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006040
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 32: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006041
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 33: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006042
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 34: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006043
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 35: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006044
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 36: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006045
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 4 Slide 37: Market, Paramaribo Streets & Zorg en Hoop Airfield., 006046
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 3: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006047
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 5: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006048
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 6: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006049
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 7: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006050
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 8: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006051
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 9: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006052
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 10: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006053
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 11: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006054
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 13: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006055
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 14: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006056
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 15: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006057
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 16: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006058
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 18: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006059
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 19: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006060
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 20: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006061
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 22: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006062
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 23: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006063
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 24: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006064
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 26: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006065
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 27: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006066
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 29: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006067
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 30: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006068
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 32: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006069
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 33: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006070
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 34: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006071
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 5 Slide 36: Leaving Zorg en Hoop, over Jungle Tafelberg., 006072
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 2: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006073
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 3: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006074
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 5: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006075
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 6: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006076
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 7: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006077
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 8: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006078
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 9: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006079
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 10: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006080
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 12: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006081
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 13: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006082
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 14: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006083
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 15: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006084
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 17: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006085
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 28: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006086
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 29: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006087
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 30: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006088
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 31: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006089
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 32: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006090
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 33: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006091
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 6 Slide 34: Planes at Kayser, Arrival at Kayser, Bird Watching at Kayser., 006092
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 1: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006093
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 2: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006094
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 3: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006095
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 4: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006096
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 6: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006097
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 8: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006098
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 9: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006099
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 11: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006100
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 12: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006101
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 13: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006102
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 14: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006103
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 16: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006104
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 17: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006105
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 18: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006106
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 19: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006107
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 21: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006108
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 22: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006109
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 24: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006110
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 25: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006111
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 26: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006112
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 27: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006113
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 28: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006114
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 29: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006115
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 30: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006116
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 31: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006117
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 32: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006118
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 33: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006119
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 34: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006120
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 7 Slide 35: Planes, Buildings & Birds Watching at Kayser, 006121
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 16: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006122
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 17: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006123
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 18: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006124
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 20: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006125
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 21: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006126
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 22: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006127
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 23: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006128
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 25: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006129
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 26: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006130
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 27: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006131
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 28: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006132
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 30: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006133
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 31: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006134
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 32: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006135
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 33: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006136
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 35: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006137
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 8 Slide 36: Builidings & Living Quarters at Kayser, 006138
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 1: Buildings at Kayser, 006139
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 3: Buildings at Kayser, 006140
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 4: Buildings at Kayser, 006141
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 5: Buildings at Kayser, 006142
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 6: Buildings at Kayser, 006143
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 7: Buildings at Kayser, 006144
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 9: Buildings at Kayser, 006145
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 10: Buildings at Kayser, 006146
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 12: Buildings at Kayser, 006147
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 13: Buildings at Kayser, 006148
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 14: Buildings at Kayser, 006149
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 16: Buildings at Kayser, 006150
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 17: Buildings at Kayser, 006151
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 18: Buildings at Kayser, 006152
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 19: Buildings at Kayser, 006153
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 20: Buildings at Kayser, 006154
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 21: Buildings at Kayser, 006155
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 23: Buildings at Kayser, 006156
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 24: Buildings at Kayser, 006157
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 25: Buildings at Kayser, 006158
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 26: Buildings at Kayser, 006159
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 27: Buildings at Kayser, 006160
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 28: Buildings at Kayser, 006161
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 29: Buildings at Kayser, 006162
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 31: Buildings at Kayser, 006163
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 33: Buildings at Kayser, 006164
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 35: Buildings at Kayser, 006165
    - Suriname Photographs. Box 9 Slide 36: Buildings at Kayser, 006166